Guide to the American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1899-2008.
American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records,
- Series II. Administration
  - Consumer Interests and Standards
    - Consumer speeches, consumerism, 1960-1966; 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Textiles and clothing, 1964 (Box 127)
    - Research projects-housing, consumer credit (Box 127)
    - Consumer publications-U.S. government (Box 127)
    - Consumer research-trading stamps (Box 127)
    - Consumer Education Service newsletters, 1936-1937 (Box 127)
    - Consumer Education Service newsletter, 1948-05 (Box 127)
    - Consumer education and standards publications (Box 127)
    - "Truth in Lending" by Richard L. D. Morse, 1966 (Box 127)
    - Consumer Information Conference program, Ohio, 1950 (Box 127)
    - "Consumer Credit Computations", 1966 (Box 127)
    - "Household Purchasing," AHEA, 1930 (Box 127)
    - "Scientific Consumer Purchasing", 1932 (Box 127)
    - "Translating Sympathy for Deceived Consumers into Effective Programs for Protection", 1966-01 (Box 127)
    - "Consumer-Buying in the Educational Program for Homemaking", 1935 (Box 127)
    - "Sources of Supplementary Materials for Courses in Consumer Education", 1940 (Box 127)
    - "Building Sound Consumer-Business Relations", 1943 (Box 127)
    - AHEA statement to Federal Trade Commission, 1968 (Box 127)
    - National Conference on Consumer Education registration list, 1939 (Box 127)
    - Statement on consumer's role in the national economy, 1964 (Box 127)
    - Standards (articles), 1931-1934 (Box 127)
    - Standardization-refrigerators, circa 1930 (Box 127)
    - "Facts You Should Know" radio program, 1949 (Box 127)
    - National Consumers Advisory Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 127)
    - Dress patterns (standardization), circa 1930-1949 (Box 127)
    - National Retail Dry Goods Association, circa 1930 (Box 127)
    - Consumer Clearing House, 1943-1944 (Box 127)
    - Consumers, 1957-1958 (Box 127)
    - Canadian Engineering Standards Association newsletters, 1934-1936 (Box 127)
    - Consumer's Age, 1934-1935 (Box 127)
    - Consumer Defender and other consumer publications, 1934 (Box 127)
    - Flammable fabrics, 1952 (Box 127)
    - Consumer issues publications, circa 1940-1969 (Box 127)
    - Standards for consumer goods, circa 1920-1939, 1942 (Box 127)
    - Standards - business and consumer acceptance, 1929-1935 (Box 127)
    - Consumer interests - publications on standards, circa 1940-1959 (Box 127)
    - Standardization-blankets, 1925-1932 (Box 127)
    - Blanket standardization, 1931-1932 (Box 127)
    - Soap and detergents (Box 127)
    - Conference papers and speeches on consumer standards (Box 127)
    - Sheeting standards, circa 1920-1939 (Box 127)
    - Sheeting standardization, 1928-1935 (Box 126)
    - Sheeting standardization (Box 126)
    - Sheeting standardization, 1929-1931 (Box 126)
    - Standardization - sheeting, circa 1930 (Box 126)
    - Consumer purchasing leaflets, circa 1930 (Box 126)
    - Early reports of the Textile Section, circa 1920 (Box 126)
    - Textile Research by the Section and Association Fellows, 1922 (Box 126)
    - Articles by AHEA members (Box 126)
    - Reports and studies, examples of Association and State Association activities (Box 126)
    - Outlines for the Study of Consumer Buying, 1936; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Peanut butter standard, circa 1950 (Box 126)
    - Commodity Standards, Division of Commerce, 1951-1952 (Box 126)
    - Body measurements (Box 126)
    - Poultry statements, USDA (Box 126)
    - Orange juice standards, circa 1960 (Box 126)
    - Standardization-textiles and orange juice, 1960 (Box 126)
    - Ham standards, circa 1960 (Box 126)
    - Electric sewing machine standards (FTC), circa 1960 (Box 126)
    - Standards, 1932, 1948-1950 (Box 126)
    - Clothing standards, 1944, 1968 (Box 126)
    - Standardization, 1931-1933 (Box 126)
    - Bread standards, 1950 (Box 126)
    - Cooperative League News Service, circa 1930 (Box 126)
    - Consumer buying-State Committees and Student Home Economics Clubs (Box 126)
    - List of extension workers, USDA, 1933 (Box 126)
    - Federal Trade Commission, Conference on Public Deception, 1959 (Box 126)
    - Consumer interests and consumer education publications (Box 126)
    - Consumer Research Council, Consumers' Testing, circa 1920-1954 (Box 126)
    - Institute of Standards, 1940 (Box 126)
    - Consumers' Standardization Council, circa 1920-1939 (Box 126)
    - Committee on Standards of Living, 1944 (Box 126)
    - Consumer education, circa 1940; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - AHEA Labeling Statement, 1970 (Box 126)
    - Standards for consumer goods, 1928-1941 (Box 126)
    - Consumer education statement (Box 126)
    - Department of Labor-Consumers' Project, food standards report, 1937 (Box 126)
    - Women's Joint Congressional Committee speech, 1936 (Box 126)
    - Excerpts from Farmer's Week, 1939 (Box 126)
    - Solving the Buying Problems of Consumers, speech, 1937 (Box 126)
    - Consumer education, 1938-1941 (Box 126)
    - Conference on Consumer Education in the Schools, 1934 (Box 126)
    - Consumer legislation, 1939-1940 (Box 126)
    - Cooperative League (Box 126)
    - Consumer education, 1940 (Box 126)
    - Consumer Project-Institute of Life Insurance, 1970 (Box 126)
    - Statements on consumer interests, consumer education [contains photographs], 1964-1971 (Box 126)
    - More Intelligent Buying-A Study Program, 1931 (Box 126)
    - Consumer purchasing, 1930-1932 (Box 126)
    - Consumer goods and standards, circa 1930 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence-"Handbook of Buying" and labeling, Mabel V. Campbell, 1934 (Box 126)
    - Consumer Advisory Council, 1962-1967; 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Committee on Consumer Relations in Advertising, Inc., 1940 (Box 126)
    - Baking utensils, American National Standards Institute, 1979 (Box 126)
    - Consumer Credit in Family Financial Management workshop, 1967 (Box 126)
    - Bibliographies of articles on consumer topics in the Journal of Home Economics, 1947-1949, 1957-1962 (Box 126)
    - Consumer retailing scrapbook, 1937-1938 (Box 59)
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    These files largely originate from the office of the Executive Director and represent the Association's activities on a wide variety of topics.
    - Executive Director chronological file, 1986-1989; 17 folders (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-ABC, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-JKL, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-MNO, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-PQR, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-ABC, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-DEF, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-GHI, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-XYZ, 1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-UVW, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-ST, 1957-1958 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-JKL, 1961-1965 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence-XYZ, 1986-1988 (Box 266)
    - Executive Secretary reports, 1923-1934 (Box 226)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1979; 5 folders (Box 226)
    - Abel, Mary Hinman and John J., 1923-1938 (Box 226)
    - Bigelow, Howard P. (Box 226)
    - Blood, Alice (Box 226)
    - DeVuyst, Paul (Box 226)
    - Amoss, Sarah Evelyn Breed (Box 226)
    - Alexander, Lucy (Box 226)
    - American Association of University Women, 1946 (Box 226)
    - Andrews, Benjamin (Box 226)
    - Associated Country Women of the World, 1934-1935 (Box 226)
    - Report of the Committee on Historical Materials, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Bureau of Human Nutrition and Home Economics-USDA, 1925-1948 (Box 226)
    - Bureau of Home Economics and the milling industry, 1934 (Box 226)
    - Ansley, Katherine McFarland (Box 226)
    - Baldwin, Keturah (Box 226)
    - Bevier, Isabel (Box 226)
    - Bane, Lita (Box 226)
    - Baylor, Adelaide S. (Box 226)
    - Berry, Josephine (Box 226)
    - Better Homes in America, 1929 (Box 226)
    - Bond, Helen Judy (Box 226)
    - Books reviewed, 1947-1949 (Box 226)
    - Brown, Muriel W. (Box 226)
    - AHEA history, members and annual meetings, 1914-1957 (Box 226)
    - Information-cooking utensils, consumer education, home economics courses, home economics abroad, 1929-1940 (Box 226)
    - Cafeterias-history and origin (Box 226)
    - Chicago Fair, contemplated exhibit on home life, 1931-1933 (Box 226)
    - D-miscellaneous, 1938-1945 (Box 226)
    - Daniels, Amy L. (Box 226)
    - Demarest, Edna Lord (Box 226)
    - Donham, S. Agnes (Box 226)
    - Erway, Dora Wetherbee (Box 226)
    - Information-E, 1933-1935 (Box 226)
    - Edwards, Alice (Box 226)
    - Employer-employee relationships in the home, 1925-1935 (Box 226)
    - Information-F, 1930-1937, 1952 (Box 226)
    - G-miscellaneous, 1925-1932 (Box 226)
    - Gearing, Mary E. (Box 226)
    - Gibbons, Rebekah (Box 226)
    - Information-H, 1929-1937 (Box 226)
    - H-miscellaneous, 1934-1956 (Box 226)
    - History of home economics (Box 226)
    - Home economics, definition of, 1930, 1950 (Box 226)
    - Home economics, purpose of and place in the educational system, 1925-1927 (Box 226)
    - Home economists, portraits, 1928-1929 (Box 226)
    - Home ownership versus renting, 1945 (Box 226)
    - Household employment and courses for household workers in public schools, 1930-1935 (Box 226)
    - Hamm, John E. (Box 226)
    - Home economics courses in colleges, 1926-1932 (Box 226)
    - Caroline L. Hunt Memorial Fund, 1927-1935 (Box 226)
    - Report of Committee on Criteria for Evaluating Various Types of Illustrative Material, 1936 (Box 226)
    - I-miscellaneous, 1922-1928 (Box 226)
    - Jones, Nellie Kedzie (Box 226)
    - Jacobs, Emma S. (Box 226)
    - Journal of Home Economics, 1923-1939 (Box 226)
    - Journal of Home Economics, 1949-1951 (Box 226)
    - Journal of Home Economics abstracts (Box 226)
    - Kumler, Katherine (Box 226)
    - Information-L, 1953 (Box 226)
    - Langworthy, Charles Ford (Box 226)
    - L-miscellaneous, 1936 (Box 226)
    - Information-N, 1927-1935 (Box 226)
    - Norton, Alice P. (Box 226)
    - Marlatt, Abby L. (Box 226)
    - McGinnis, Esther (Box 226)
    - M-miscellaneous, 1926, 1947-1950 (Box 226)
    - Merrill-Palmer School Conference on American Participation in International Problems of Education, 1931 (Box 226)
    - Milam, Ava (Box 99)
    - Information-N, 1936 (Box 99)
    - O-miscellaneous, 1936-1939, 1954 (Box 99)
    - Pan-Pacific Women's Association, 1936-1937 (Box 99)
    - P-miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 99)
    - Women's Advisory Council on Poverty (Box 99)
    - Regional annual meetings, circa 1981 (Box 99)
    - Teen Attitude Study: A Nationwide Study of Teenagers' Concerns and Views, 1988 (Box 99)
    - Seven Lamps of Home (Box 99)
    - Workshop on Aging, 1960-1962; 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, Marie Dye: Outline for a History of AHEA; AHEA Foundation/AHEA Fund, 1960-1974 (Box 99)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1989, 1993 (Box 99)
    - Correspondence, Ginger Sunai, 1985-1986 (Box 99)
    - A Nation for Families: A Study of Family Life Education in Public Schools
      - Publication rights, 1985 (Box 99)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 99)
      - Correspondence (Box 99)
      - Inquiries, 1984 (Box 99)
      - Charts (Box 99)
    - NAF/CFF Family Life Education Handbook production costs, 1983 (Box 99)
    - National Academy for Families, 1982-1983 (Box 99)
    - NAF research for book (Box 99)
    - Home economics research (domestic), 1984-1985 (Box 99)
    - W-167, research project on families and stress, 1983-1984 (Box 99)
    - Sheek article for Journal of Home Economics (Box 99)
    - Family Life Education Handbook, CFF/NAF bills (Box 99)
    - Fundraising, external funding, 1977-1985 (Box 99)
    - Clorox proposal, 1982 (Box 99)
    - Family Life Education, workshop, curriculum (Box 99)
    - FDA Background Conference on Nutrient Labeling, 1973 (Box 99)
    - Curriculum Study of College Programs, 1946-1947 (Box 99)
    - Improving Research in Home Economics, Cornell University, 1965 (Box 99)
    - AHEA Profile: Home Economists in Action, 1965 (Box 99)
    - AHEA history: publications, writings, 1934-1939 (Box 99)
    - Division and department correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 99)
    - Education advertising, 1959 (Box 99)
    - Home Economics Secondary School teachers (Box 99)
    - "Keys for the Homes of Tomorrow" (Sears film) script and correspondence, 1964 (Box 99)
    - Directories of state supervisors of Home Economics Education (Box 99)
    - Education priority briefing, 1977 (Box 99)
    - Eastern regional meeting, 1979 (Box 99)
    - Introduction, conclusion: Integrative Themes in the Content of Home Economics and Their Impact on Families, 1984 (Box 99)
    - Strategic marketing planning, 1988 (Box 99)
    - Lever Brothers teen survey, 1988; 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Silk coverlet cards (Box 99)
    - Finished Foods-A First Report, 1961 (Box 99)
    - "Home Economics Combats Economic Illiteracy," American Vocation Journal (Box 99)
    - Family Life Education Project, Esther McGinnis, 1952 (Box 99)
    - Family Life Education Project, 1951-1952 (Box 99)
    - The Grant Foundation, Inc., Family Life Education Project, 1951-1952 (Box 99)
    - Family Life Education conferences and workshops, 1951-1952 (Box 99)
    - Family life education and research: reports and publications, 1941-1965 (Box 4)
    - National Council on Family Relations (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Executive Board, Executive Committee correspondence, 1933-1939, 1950-1970 (Box 4)
    - Johnson Home Economics Interest Inventory of College Students, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Home economics careers, 1950-1978 (Box 4)
    - Information about Career Guidance: correspondence, reports, circa 1960 (Box 4)
    - Civil Defense: correspondence, 1955 (Box 4)
    - Awards (Journal of Home Economics and ads for corporations), 1951 (Box 4)
    - Outstanding home economists: correspondence, publications, 1923-1968 (Box 4)
    - Policies, 1936-1966 (Box 4)
    - Policy correspondence, 1929-1970 (Box 4)
    - Radio-TV interview script (60th anniversary), 1969 (Box 4)
    - Field Service policies and procedures and other policy correspondence, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Policy Handbook, 1966 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, Alice Edwards, 1928-1935 (Box 4)
    - Working with Low Income Families workshop, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
    - Rehabilitation of the Physically Handicapped in Homemaking Activities workshop, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Expanding the Services of the Home Economist in Rehabilitation workshop, 1960 (Box 4)
    - Rehabilitation of the Physically Handicapped in Homemaking Activities workshop, 1963; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Functional Fashions for the Physically Handicapped (Box 4)
    - Casual letters from VIPs and their signatures, 1918-1955 (Box 4)
    - Placement services, 1944-1947 (Box 4)
    - AHEA history (Box 4)
    - Low-income families workshop, 1965-1966 (Box 4)
    - Home Economics and Housing conferences, 1934-1935 (Box 4)
    - National Outlook Conference on Rural Youth, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Workshop on Utilization and Training of Auxiliary Personnel in Home Economics, final report, 1970-06 (Box 4)
    - Workshop for Auxiliary Workers in Home Economics grant, Office of Education, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Home economics rehabilitation fellowship program, 1970-1973 (Box 4)
    - Home economics rehabilitation graduate traineeships, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
    - Report of the Pilot AHEA-RSA Internship for Home Economics in Rehabilitation, 1970-07-1970-08 (Box 4)
    - Future Directions for Home Economics in Rehabilitation workshop, 1969 (Box 4)
    - National Bureau of Standards grant, U.S. Metric Study, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Parent education and family life (Box 4)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Report on Participation of Minority Home Economists in AHEA National Offices, 1970-1977 (Box 4)
    - Computer-Assisted Instruction in Home Economics workshop brochure, 1972 (Box 4)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Administration, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Rehabilitation Services Administration grant, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Rehabilitation grant audit (for 1962-1965), 1966 (Box 5)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Administration, 1962-1964, 1967-1968; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Rehabilitation Services Administration, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Home economics in higher education: correspondence, 1946-1951 (Box 5)
    - Chicago workshop of the Committee for Evaluating College Programs of Home Economics, 1947; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Home economics in higher education, 1947-1950 (Box 5)
    - Donation of AHEA Saga, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Directory of Private Funding Sources for Home Economics-Related Programs; Directory of Public Funding Sources for Home Economics-Related Programs, 1977; 1978 (Box 5)
    - Home Economics in Higher Education workshop, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Speeches and articles from AHEA officers and staff, 1951-1963 (Box 5)
    - Speeches and articles from AHEA officers and staff, 1928-1965 (Box 5)
    - Home Economics Week, 1955-1958 (Box 5)
    - Biography of an Idea, Keturah Baldwin (Box 5)
    - Marketing FACS, AVA national convention, 1994 (Box 5)
    - Home Economist Image Study, Daniel Yankelovich, 1974 (Box 5)
    - AHEA Blueprint for Progress, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Interview with [Willa Vaughn] Tinsley, [Keturah] Baldwin and [Doris] Hanson (typescript) (Box 5)
    - Home Economics name change, 1966-1972 (Box 5)
    - Program Task Force/Operational Task Force/Workbook for Corporate Planning, circa 1973 (Box 5)
    - Cooperative testing, Gwen Cooke, 1950, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Low-Income Workshop evaluation, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
    - Home Economics in Rehabilitation (AHEA-VRA advisory group, grant project), 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - Social and Rehabilitation Service Grant, 1968-1973; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Rehabilitation Services Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
    - RSA training grant and short term pilot internship, 1970-1975 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, minutes and reports, 1965-1971 (Box 5)
    - "Home Economist Image Study: A Qualitative Investigation," Daniel Yankelovich Inc., 1974 (Box 5)
    - Yankelovich image study, correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 5)
    - Development of Individualized Competency-Based Modules for Supervising Teachers, project summary, Hester R. Stewart (Box 5)
    - AHEA governance directory; Minority Participation in Dietetics/Nutrition for Project 2000 Summit, 1989-1990; 1990; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Displaced Homemakers: Program Options, guide for national training conference, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Home Economics Concepts: A Base for Curriculum Development (typescript), 1989 (Box 6)
    - Summer Camp/Institute for Prospective Teachers, Phi Delta Kappa International, 1987 (Box 6)
    - NGO Committee on the Family, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Association law and finances, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Coalition for Vocational Home Economics Education, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Extension service funding: correspondence, publications, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    - Annual goal setting, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, Julie Lockway (CFF Project Assistant), 1985-1986 (Box 6)
    - Mid-Career Home Economics Administrators Workshop, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Home Economics Defined Conferences participant lists, 1979 (Box 6)
    - Coalition of Family Organizations, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Membership: statistics and reports, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Membership correspondence, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Forrest T. Jones & Company Insurance, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Idaho HEA; Student Member Section, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Global Connections: A Development Education Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
    - Library of Congress, Youth Reference Service, 1945 (Box 6)
    - Nutrition education research, 1976, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Women's issues (Box 6)
    - "Home Economists: Not Perfect But Close" bumper sticker (Box 6)
    - Home economics research, miscellaneous historical materials, 1948-1963 (Box 6)
    - The Philosophical Context of AHEA, Components of AHEA, Assumptions and Interpretations: report, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Home economics research, 1953-1957 (Box 6)
    - Aging, 1953-1963 (Box 6)
    - Home Economics, explanations of (definitions), 1958-1961 (Box 6)
    - Homemaker service and the home economist, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
    - Metric committee (Box 6)
    - The "Image" of Occupational Education in North Carolina, FY1972: An Evaluation Study and a Model (Box 6)
    - Speech material, 1968-1973 (Box 6)
    - Proposals, 1968-1974 (Box 6)
    - AHEA objectives and philosophy (Box 6)
    - Purdue study (household employment), 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Special planning grant, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Sex education, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
    - Statistics: health, employment, degrees (Box 6)
    - The Legislative Process: Becoming an Effective Advocate (Home Economics Public Policy Council/AHEA), 1991 (Box 6)
    - National Library Week, 1959 (Box 6)
    - Truth-in-packaging bill, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
    - Truth-in-packaging bill, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Truth-in-packaging and Labeling, 1965-1973 (Box 308)
    - Truth-in-lending Act, 1967 (Box 308)
    - Quality Stabilization Act, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Legislative correspondence, 1954-1964 (Box 6)
    - Mahogany bill, 1963 (Box 6)
    - Beef grading: statements and correspondence, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Affiliations with other organizations, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
    - Master's and doctor's degrees in Home Economic subjects conferred, 1948-05-1948-12 (Box 6)
    - Legislative correspondence and statements, 1948-1963 (Box 6)
    - Truth-in-lending bill, 1960-1962 (Box 6)
    - Legislative correspondence and statements, 1952-1953 (Box 6)
    - Legislative correspondence and statements, 1958-1959 (Box 6)
    - Legislative correspondence and newsletters, 1961-1962 (Box 6)
    - "Our Intellectual Ecology: A Treatise on Home Economics," Kinsey B. Green, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Proposal to the Associate Manpower Administrator for Policy, Evaluation, and Research, Manpower Administration, U. S. Dept. of Labor for a Contract for a Research and Development Project, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Determining Directions for Curriculum Development in Home Economics, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Home economics name change, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Family Life Education Secondary Significant Issues, Richard N. Hey (conference presentation), 1968 (Box 6)
    - Lists of names of college/university programs other than home economics, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Metric information (Box 6)
    - Planned giving, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Association jewelry correspondence, 1936 (Box 6)
    - Child Care Center: Resource Materials Packet, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Financial information, 1977-1982 (Box 6)
    - Guest book, international visitors, 1947 (Box 6)
    - Speech material, 1982-1988 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 38)
    - Articles on home economics, 1961-1965 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous family planning reports, 1971-1974 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous papers on home economics, 1963, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Identification of people in Lake Placid photographs, 1928, 1950 (Box 38)
    - Foreign holidays: writings on holidays in non-U.S. countries (Box 38)
    - Supervisory workshops, 1978 (Box 38)
    - Proposed program plans, sections, 1986 (Box 38)
    - Section annual reports, 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - AHEA semi-annual program report, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Semi-annual program reports, 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - Proposed program plans, sections, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Section programs of work, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Program of Work forms received-Professional section, 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - Program of Work forms received-Subject-Matter section, 1984-1985 (Box 38)
    - Public policy, 1984 (Box 38)
    - Millie Riley, Washington Dateline correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 38)
    - Consumer and Homemaker Education budget restoration effort, 1985 (Box 38)